So now that we did the sign in, let me also click on upgrade to show you the plans and
pricing that this tool has and provides us with.
So as you see, it also submitted the command that I gave it automatically, but...
So as you see, it says keep creating with a seven day free trial, and these are the plans
that we have with Adobe Firefly.
The standard is, so these are Canadian dollars as you see, like $13 per month, and
Firefly Pro is, again, 13 per month, yeah, it has an offer in a weird way, and we also have
Firefly Premiere, which is $262 Canadian dollars per month.
Yes, so these are the plans and pricing for this very tool.
I close this one, and as you see...